[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "In the end, was it the lack of forensic evidence which you think led to this acquittal?", "question_tokens": ["In", "the", "end", ",", "was", "it", "the", "lack", "of", "forensic", "evidence", "which", "you", "think", "led", "to", "this", "acquittal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, in my mind it is, because the state really didn't have any valid evidence to go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "my", "mind", "it", "is", ",", "because", "the", "state", "really", "did", "n't", "have", "any", "valid", "evidence", "to", "go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "From everything that you saw, from everything that you examined, did you ever see evidence of premeditated murder?", "question_tokens": ["From", "everything", "that", "you", "saw", ",", "from", "everything", "that", "you", "examined", ",", "did", "you", "ever", "see", "evidence", "of", "premeditated", "murder", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "No, and that was one of the problems that the prosecution had is there was no cause of death.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "and", "that", "was", "one", "of", "the", "problems", "that", "the", "prosecution", "had", "is", "there", "was", "no", "cause", "of", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "I mean, do you have any personal feeling about what you think happened to her?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "have", "any", "personal", "feeling", "about", "what", "you", "think", "happened", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "You know, I really don't want to speculate.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "speculate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "But did you see anything -- when you examined Caylee's remains, did you see anything that would go along with that theory, that would corroborate it in any way?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "see", "anything", "--", "when", "you", "examined", "Caylee", "'s", "remains", ",", "did", "you", "see", "anything", "that", "would", "go", "along", "with", "that", "theory", ",", "that", "would", "corroborate", "it", "in", "any", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "EICHS: Well, one of the things that forensic anthropologists look for is manner of death or cause of death.", "answer_tokens": ["EICHS", ":", "Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "forensic", "anthropologists", "look", "for", "is", "manner", "of", "death", "or", "cause", "of", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Caylee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "On the other hand, it's been a hell of an ordeal for them, and if she is innocent, as this jury has decided that she is, you can understand that explosion of emotion at the end, can't you?", "question_tokens": ["On", "the", "other", "hand", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "hell", "of", "an", "ordeal", "for", "them", ",", "and", "if", "she", "is", "innocent", ",", "as", "this", "jury", "has", "decided", "that", "she", "is", ",", "you", "can", "understand", "that", "explosion", "of", "emotion", "at", "the", "end", ",", "ca", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "I mean, from a legal point of view, were you surprised at the verdict?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "from", "a", "legal", "point", "of", "view", ",", "were", "you", "surprised", "at", "the", "verdict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "You're always surprised at verdicts in cases like this.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "always", "surprised", "at", "verdicts", "in", "cases", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, I think it's fringe science.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "fringe", "science", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "So there are some very big unanswered questions here, aren't there?", "question_tokens": ["So", "there", "are", "some", "very", "big", "unanswered", "questions", "here", ",", "are", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "You are so right, Piers, and everybody in America and all over the world who are following this know that in their gut, in their heart of hearts, people are upset about this verdict.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "so", "right", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "everybody", "in", "America", "and", "all", "over", "the", "world", "who", "are", "following", "this", "know", "that", "in", "their", "gut", ",", "in", "their", "heart", "of", "hearts", ",", "people", "are", "upset", "about", "this", "verdict", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Rodney King"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "What is that moment like when you realize that it's going against all popular thought and actually you're going to lose the case?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "moment", "like", "when", "you", "realize", "that", "it", "'s", "going", "against", "all", "popular", "thought", "and", "actually", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "lose", "the", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, Piers, to tell you the truth, it's really not like that because there was predictions that we were going to lose this case or at least not be able to convict from long before we even started to pick the jury because of a variety of issues including celebrity, race, the Rodney King riots.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "to", "tell", "you", "the", "truth", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "not", "like", "that", "because", "there", "was", "predictions", "that", "we", "were", "going", "to", "lose", "this", "case", "or", "at", "least", "not", "be", "able", "to", "convict", "from", "long", "before", "we", "even", "started", "to", "pick", "the", "jury", "because", "of", "a", "variety", "of", "issues", "including", "celebrity", ",", "race", ",", "the", "Rodney", "King", "riots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ":", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Is this not the problem with having cameras in these courtrooms?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "not", "the", "problem", "with", "having", "cameras", "in", "these", "courtrooms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, I'm very proud that we have the First Amendment here in America and we can shine the light on all three of our branches of government -- legislative, executive, and judicial.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "very", "proud", "that", "we", "have", "the", "First", "Amendment", "here", "in", "America", "and", "we", "can", "shine", "the", "light", "on", "all", "three", "of", "our", "branches", "of", "government", "--", "legislative", ",", "executive", ",", "and", "judicial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "I mean if a legal system isn't based on truth and justice, then what kind of system is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "a", "legal", "system", "is", "n't", "based", "on", "truth", "and", "justice", ",", "then", "what", "kind", "of", "system", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, if you want truth, get scientists.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "want", "truth", ",", "get", "scientists", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What happens to Casey Anthony next?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happens", "to", "Casey", "Anthony", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "On Thursday is her sentencing.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "Thursday", "is", "her", "sentencing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa Bloom", "Marcia"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ":", "NN", ",", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "But explain why a skilled attorney would raise an issue of abuse?", "question_tokens": ["But", "explain", "why", "a", "skilled", "attorney", "would", "raise", "an", "issue", "of", "abuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Lisa Bloom, Marcia -- oh, go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Lisa", "Bloom", ",", "Marcia", "--", "oh", ",", "go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Alan?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I'm just wondering why a skilled attorney would raise allegations which he couldn't prove of sexual abuse by the father of the daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "wondering", "why", "a", "skilled", "attorney", "would", "raise", "allegations", "which", "he", "could", "n't", "prove", "of", "sexual", "abuse", "by", "the", "father", "of", "the", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Did you predict this not guilty verdict?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "predict", "this", "not", "guilty", "verdict", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, I actually predicted the best-case scenario for the defense would be a hung jury.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "actually", "predicted", "the", "best-case", "scenario", "for", "the", "defense", "would", "be", "a", "hung", "jury", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "I mean, can the results of these cases literally fall down on one or two or three jurors and the selection process?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "can", "the", "results", "of", "these", "cases", "literally", "fall", "down", "on", "one", "or", "two", "or", "three", "jurors", "and", "the", "selection", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, it can.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Do you think that was help informal the end to Casey Anthony?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "was", "help", "informal", "the", "end", "to", "Casey", "Anthony", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, we didn't really focus on the demographics.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "did", "n't", "really", "focus", "on", "the", "demographics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Why do you need them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "need", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Very quickly, we don't have star chamber justice in this country.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "star", "chamber", "justice", "in", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "I mean, how on Earth does this family even attempt to rebuild any kind of relationship here, given what went on in the courtroom?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "on", "Earth", "does", "this", "family", "even", "attempt", "to", "rebuild", "any", "kind", "of", "relationship", "here", ",", "given", "what", "went", "on", "in", "the", "courtroom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I don't think they do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "What was your gut feeling when that verdict came in?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "gut", "feeling", "when", "that", "verdict", "came", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "That I wasn't that surprised.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "I", "was", "n't", "that", "surprised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "But, Drew, listen, I take that point, but have you ever in your entire career come across a mother who has lost a child and doesn't report that for 31 days?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "Drew", ",", "listen", ",", "I", "take", "that", "point", ",", "but", "have", "you", "ever", "in", "your", "entire", "career", "come", "across", "a", "mother", "who", "has", "lost", "a", "child", "and", "does", "n't", "report", "that", "for", "31", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I have not encountered that specific experience, but I've encountered -- this case -- Casey reminds me of several of my patients, frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "not", "encountered", "that", "specific", "experience", ",", "but", "I", "'ve", "encountered", "--", "this", "case", "--", "Casey", "reminds", "me", "of", "several", "of", "my", "patients", ",", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Brad Conway, finally, do you agree with Dr. Drew that there's really no way back for this family, in terms of any relationship between the parents and their daughter?", "question_tokens": ["Brad", "Conway", ",", "finally", ",", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "Dr.", "Drew", "that", "there", "'s", "really", "no", "way", "back", "for", "this", "family", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "any", "relationship", "between", "the", "parents", "and", "their", "daughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Probably, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad Conway", "Dr. Drew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "When it's high profile, when it's famous, predicting a verdict is almost impossible, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "it", "'s", "high", "profile", ",", "when", "it", "'s", "famous", ",", "predicting", "a", "verdict", "is", "almost", "impossible", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110705pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "But what didn't make any sense either -- and I keep coming back to this -- is what kind of mother who loses a child doesn't report it for more than a month?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "did", "n't", "make", "any", "sense", "either", "--", "and", "I", "keep", "coming", "back", "to", "this", "--", "is", "what", "kind", "of", "mother", "who", "loses", "a", "child", "does", "n't", "report", "it", "for", "more", "than", "a", "month", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "You're right, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "right", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]